<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on Ptah Documentation</title>
    <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on Ptah Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/glossary/</guid>
      <description> Terms:  Ptah Landing Page Builder = Ptah Builder = Ptah - the open-source landing page builder for video games Sections Library Elements Library  Ptah Editor:  Navigation Panel - a sidebar on the left with the settings menu Settings Panel - a sidebar on the left with the Sections list and the elements properties Preview Area - a preview area for content the Resizing tool rectangle the Settings icon  Ptah Dashboard:  the landing pages list the Create new landing button  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a section</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/add-section/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/add-section/</guid>
      <description>Using ready-made sections Ptah Builder allows you to create and adjust the content of your web-page and automatically saves all changes.
The sidebar on the left gives you access to all web-elements of your landing page. We call this the Settings Panel. The Settings Panel allows you to view and adjust Properties of any object you have already added. You can learn more about objects properties.
After you make a change on Settings Panel the content on the right on Preview Area will be updated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Properties</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/background/</guid>
      <description>Background properties There are several ways to fill a page or section background:
 Color fill Gradient Image background Fullscreen video background Color overlay  To edit a section background, you need to open Settings Panel to adjust Properties:
 click the Background icon on hover over the section in Preview Area. or click the same icon on Settings Panel at the end of the section&amp;rsquo;s title.   TODO image</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content alignment</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/align/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/align/</guid>
      <description>Content alignment Ptah Sections is designed for responsive landing pages. You can customise the alignment of elements in a section&amp;rsquo;s blocks.
To set the alignment of a block&amp;rsquo;s content open the block properties by hover over it on Preview Area and click the Settings icon at the top-left.  Flow elements into a row or column To display elements of a block in one line click on the Row Direction icon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edit section content</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/edit-section/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/edit-section/</guid>
      <description>On-page editing The Ptah Builder makes editing pretty intuitive. You can change content and its properties right on the page in Preview Area and everything will be automatically saved.
On hover over a Block or an Element, you can view an icon to set properties at the top-left corner.
TODO КАРТИНКА лучше слайдер для секции, блока и элемента с этими иконками   Adjust block properties Set up the size and spacing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payments</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/payments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/payments/</guid>
      <description> PaySuper Payment Form PaySuper Checkout creates a secure PaySuper-hosted form that lets you collect payments with just a few lines of code. The Checkout Form loads near instantly and is designed to boost your paying conversion rate.
Try now See how the Checkout Form looks and feels BUTTON Test Payment  User flow https://docs.pay.super.com/docs/payments/quick-start/  After the payment Receipts Payouts  Payment Token Payment Links Game key </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Quick Start 1. Регистрация 2. Создаем новый landing page на дашборде. From your dashboard, you can access, create, and manage your projects.
Start from scratch or from one of our 100+ templates
Ptah lets you start your design from a completely blank canvas, so there’s no limit to your creativity. That way, you can design a truly custom website—instead of relying on a template built by someone who doesn’t know you or your company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Size and spacing</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/size/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/size/</guid>
      <description>Spacing on the page You can create extra space around elements to helps your users focus on the content, what may increases conversions.
TODO картинка  The best practice is spacing and sizing within ratios. Ptah pre-designed sections keep spacing consistent. This is how one of Ptah sections with default spacing looks like:
TODO картинка с выделенными отступами, чтобы показать как нужно их правильно делать
 Any element on your page can have spacing that immediately surrounds the element within the border (padding) and outside the border (margin).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typography</title>
      <link>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/fonts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.stg.ptah.super.com/docs/fonts/</guid>
      <description>Typography The landing page design must be on-brand. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to use from 1 to 3 typefaces. If you have more than 3 typefaces it can make your page chaotic.
Once you have chosen the right typeface, typography makes your landing page appealing and readable.
Set up fonts Ptah has a built-in Google Fonts library which offers about 1000 fonts to choose from for all your text and button needs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>